[
{
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "144",
      "options": [
        "146",
        "144",
        "136",
        "142"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "100",
      "options": [
        "110",
        "100",
        "103",
        "107"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "44",
        "41",
        "34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "12",
        "4",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 20?",
      "correctAnswer": "400",
      "options": [
        "398",
        "400",
        "392",
        "401"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "1",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 18?",
      "correctAnswer": "324",
      "options": [
        "324",
        "331",
        "318",
        "327"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "6",
        "5",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "10",
        "3",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area <br> of a square with side 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "81",
      "options": [
        "80",
        "73",
        "77",
        "81"
      ]
    }
]